<Label drug="lynparza" track="TAC2017_ADR">
  <Text>
    <Section name="adverse reactions" id="S1">    6 ADVERSE REACTIONS

  The following adverse reactions are discussed elsewhere in the labeling:



 *    Myelodysplastic syndrome/Acute Myeloid Leukemia [see    Warnings and Precautions (5.1)    ]  
 *    Pneumonitis [see    Warnings and Precautions (5.2)    ]  
   *    Most common adverse reactions (&gt;=20%) in clinical trials were anemia, nausea, fatigue (including asthenia), vomiting, diarrhea, dysgeusia, dyspepsia, headache, decreased appetite, nasopharyngitis/pharyngitis/URI, cough, arthralgia/musculoskeletal pain, myalgia, back pain, dermatitis/rash and abdominal pain/discomfort. (  6.1  ) 
 *    Most common laboratory abnormalities (&gt;=25%) were increase in creatinine, mean corpuscular volume elevation, decrease in hemoglobin, decrease in lymphocytes, decrease in absolute neutrophil count, and decrease in platelets. (  6.1  ) 
      EXCERPT:   To report SUSPECTED ADVERSE REACTIONS, contact AstraZeneca at 1-800-236-9933 or FDA at 1-800-FDA-1088 or  www.fda.gov/medwatch.  
 

 

  6.1 Clinical Trial Experience

  Because clinical trials are conducted under widely varying conditions, adverse reaction rates observed in the clinical trials of a drug cannot be directly compared to rates in the clinical trials of another drug and may not reflect the rates observed in practice.



 Lynparza 400 mg twice daily as monotherapy, has been studied in 300 patients with g  BRCA  -mutated advanced ovarian cancer, and 223 of these patients had received 3 or more prior lines of chemotherapy.



 In the 223 patients with g  BRCA  -mutated ovarian cancer who received 3 or more prior lines of chemotherapy (including 137 patients in Study 1 with measureable disease)  [see      Clinical Studies (14)      ]  , adverse reactions led to dose interruption in 40% of patients, dose reduction in 4%, and discontinuation in 7%. There were 8 (4%) patients with adverse reactions leading to death, two were attributed to acute leukemia, and one each was attributed to COPD, cerebrovascular accident, intestinal perforation, pulmonary embolism, sepsis, and suture rupture. Table 1 presents the frequency of adverse reactions reported in &gt;=20% of 223 patients (in 6 studies) with g  BRCA  -mutated advanced ovarian cancer who had received 3 or more prior lines of chemotherapy who were treated with Lynparza 400 mg twice daily. The median exposure to Lynparza in these patients was 158 days.



 Table 1 Adverse Reactions Reported in &gt;=20% of Patients with gBRCA-Mutated Advanced Ovarian Cancer Receiving Lynparza 
                                                       3 or more lines of prior chemotherapy    
  Adverse Reaction                                     Grades 1-4  N=223  %    Grades 3-4  N=223  %    
  Blood and Lymphatic disorders                        
                                                      Anemia                                              
                                                                                                            34                      18                     
  Gastrointestinal disorders                           
                                                      Abdominal pain/discomfort                           
                                                                                                            43                      8                      
                                                      Decreased appetite                                  
                                                                                                            22                      1                      
                                                      Nausea                                              
                                                                                                            64                      3                      
                                                      Vomiting                                            
                                                                                                            43                      4                      
                                                      Diarrhea                                            
                                                                                                            31                      1                      
                                                      Dyspepsia                                           
                                                                                                            25                      0                      
  General disorders                                    
                                                      Fatigue/asthenia                                    
                                                                                                            66                      8                      
  Infections and infestations                                                                         
                                                      Nasopharyngitis/URI                                 
                                                                                                            26                      0                      
  Musculoskeletal and Connective Tissue disorders                                                     
                                                      Arthralgia/musculoskeletal pain                     
                                                                                                            21                      0                      
                                                      Myalgia                                             
                                                                                                            22                      0                      
         Table 2 presents the frequency of abnormal laboratory findings in the 223 patients with g  BRCA  -mutated advanced ovarian cancer who had received three or more prior lines of chemotherapy receiving Lynparza 400 mg twice daily.
 

 Table 2 Laboratory Abnormalities Reported in Patients with gBRCA-Mutated Advanced Ovarian Cancer Receiving Lynparza 
  Laboratory Parameter1                                3 or more lines of prior chemotherapy    
  Grades 1-4  N=223  %                                 Grades 3-4  N=223  %    
  Decrease in hemoglobin (anemia)                      90                      15                     
  Decrease in absolute neutrophil count (neutropenia)    25                      7                      
  Decrease in platelets (thrombocytopenia)             30                      3                      
  Decrease in lymphocytes (lymphopenia)                56                      17                     
  Mean corpuscular volume elevation                    57                      -                      
  Increase in creatinine                               30                      2                      
         The following adverse reactions and laboratory abnormalities have been identified in &gt;=10 to &lt;20% of the 223 patients receiving Lynparza and not included in the table: cough, constipation, dysgeusia, peripheral edema, back pain, dizziness, headache, urinary tract infection, dyspnea, and rash. The following adverse reactions and laboratory abnormalities have been identified in &gt;=1 to &lt;10% of the 223 patients receiving Lynparza and not included in the table: leukopenia, stomatitis, peripheral neuropathy, pyrexia, hypomagnesemia, hyperglycemia, anxiety, depression, insomnia, dysuria, urinary incontinence, vulvovaginal disorder, dry skin/ eczema, pruritis, hypertension, venous thrombosis (including pulmonary embolism), and hot flush.
 

 Table 3 presents adverse reactions reported in &gt;=20% of patients from a randomized trial of Lynparza 400 mg twice daily as maintenance monotherapy compared to placebo in patients with platinum sensitive, relapsed, high-grade serous ovarian cancer following treatment with 2 or more platinum-containing regimens. Table 4 presents the laboratory abnormalities in patients from this randomized trial. Of the 96 patients with g  BRCA  -mutation, 53 received Lynparza, and 43 received placebo. The median duration on treatment with Lynparza was 11.1 months for patients with a g  BRCA  mutation compared to 4.4 months for patients with g  BRCA  mutation on placebo.



 Adverse reactions led to dose interruptions in 26% of those receiving Lynparza and 7% of those receiving placebo; dose reductions in 15% of Lynparza and 5% of placebo patients; and discontinuation in 9% of Lynparza and 0% in placebo patients. One (2%) patient on Lynparza died as a result of an adverse reaction.



 Table 3 Adverse Reactions Reported in &gt;=20% of Patients with gBRCA-Mutated Ovarian Cancer in the Randomized Trial 
  Adverse Reactions                        Lynparza  N=53    Placebo  N=43    
                                           Grades 1-4  %    Grades 3-4  %    Grades 1-4  %      Grades 3-4  %     
  Blood and Lymphatic disorders                                                                                 
                                          Anemia                                  
                                                                                    25              4               7                  2                 
  Gastrointestinal disorders               
                                          Abdominal pain/discomfort               
                                                                                    47              0               58                 2                 
                                          Decreased appetite                      
                                                                                    25              0               14                 0                 
                                          Nausea                                  
                                                                                    75              2               37                 0                 
                                          Vomiting                                
                                                                                    32              4               9                  0                 
                                          Diarrhea                                
                                                                                    28              4               21                 2                 
                                          Dyspepsia                               
                                                                                    25              0               14                 0                 
                                          Dysgeusia                               
                                                                                    21              0               9                  0                 
  General disorders                        
                                          Fatigue (including asthenia, lethargy)  
                                                                                    68              6               53                 2                 
  Infections and infestations                                                                                   
                                          Nasopharyngitis/Pharyngitis/URI         
                                                                                    43              0               16                 0                 
  Musculoskeletal and Connective tissue disorders                                                                         
                                          Arthralgia/Musculoskeletal pain         
                                                                                                   32             
                                                 4              
                                                    21                
                                                         0                
                                      
                                          Myalgia                                 
                                                                                                   25             
                                                 2              
                                                    12                
                                                         0                
                                      
                                          Back pain                               
                                                                                                   25             
                                                 6              
                                                    21                
                                                         0                
                                      
  Nervous system disorder                  
                                          Headache                                
                                                                                    25              0               19                 2                 
  Respiratory, Thoracic, Mediastinal disorders                                                                         
                                          Cough                                   
                                                                                    21              0               14                 0                 
  Skin and Subcutaneous Tissue                                                                                  
                                          Dermatitis/Rash                         
                                                                                    25              0               14                 0                 
          Table 4 Laboratory Abnormalities in Patients with gBRCA-Mutated Ovarian Cancer in the Randomized Trial 
  Laboratory parameter1                    Lynparza  N=53    Placebo  N=43    
                                           Grades 1-4  %    Grades 3-4  %    Grades 1-4  %      Grades 3-4  %     
  Decrease in hemoglobin                   85              8               58                 2                 
  Decrease in absolute neutrophil count    32              8               23                 0                 
  Decrease in platelets                    26              6               19                 0                 
  Mean corpuscular volume elevation        85              -               44                 -                 
  Increase in creatininePatients were allowed to enter clinical studies with laboratory values of CTCAE Grade 1.    26              0               5                  0                 
</Section>
    <Section name="warnings and precautions" id="S2">    5 WARNINGS AND PRECAUTIONS



   EXCERPT:    *    Myelodysplastic syndrome/Acute Myeloid Leukemia: (MDS/AML) occurred in patients exposed to Lynparza, and some cases were fatal. Monitor patients for hematological toxicity at baseline and monthly thereafter. Discontinue if MDS/AML is confirmed. (  5.1  ) 
 *    Pneumonitis: occurred in patients exposed to Lynparza, and some cases were fatal. Interrupt treatment if pneumonitis is suspected. Discontinue if pneumonitis is confirmed. (  5.2  ) 
 *    Embryo-Fetal toxicity: Lynparza can cause fetal harm. Advise females of reproductive potential of the potential risk to a fetus and to avoid pregnancy. (  5.3  ,  8.1  ) 
    
 

   5.1 Myelodysplastic syndrome/Acute Myeloid Leukemia



  Myelodysplastic syndrome/Acute Myeloid Leukemia (MDS/AML) have been confirmed in 6 out of 298 (2%) patients enrolled in a single arm trial of Lynparza monotherapy, in patients with deleterious or suspected deleterious germline BRCA  -mutated ( gBRCA  m) advanced cancers. In a randomized placebo controlled trial, MDS/AML occurred in 3 out of 136 (2%) patients with advanced ovarian cancer treated with Lynparza. Overall, MDS/AML were reported in 22 of 2,618 (&lt;1%) patients treated with Lynparza. The majority of MDS/AML cases (17 of 22 cases) were fatal, and the duration of therapy with Lynparza in patients who developed secondary MDS/cancer-therapy related AML varied from &lt;6 months to &gt;2 years. All patients had previous chemotherapy with platinum agents and/or other DNA damaging agents.



 Monitor complete blood count testing at baseline and monthly thereafter. Do not start Lynparza until patients have recovered from hematological toxicity caused by previous chemotherapy (&lt;=CTCAE Grade 1). For prolonged hematological toxicities, interrupt Lynparza and monitor blood counts weekly until recovery. If the levels have not recovered to CTCAE Grade 1 or less after 4 weeks, refer the patient to a hematologist for further investigations, including bone marrow analysis and blood sample for cytogenetics. If MDS/AML is confirmed, discontinue Lynparza.



    5.2 Pneumonitis



  Pneumonitis, including fatal cases, occurred in &lt;1% of patients treated with Lynparza. If patients present with new or worsening respiratory symptoms such as dyspnea, fever, cough, wheezing, or a radiological abnormality occurs, interrupt treatment with Lynparza and initiate prompt investigation. If pneumonitis is confirmed, discontinue Lynparza.



    5.3 Embryo-Fetal Toxicity



  Lynparza can cause fetal harm when administered to a pregnant woman based on its mechanism of action and findings in animals. Olaparib was teratogenic and caused embryo-fetal toxicity in rats at exposures below those in patients receiving the recommended human dose of 400 mg twice daily. If the patient becomes pregnant while taking this drug, apprise the patient of the potential hazard to a fetus [see     Use in Specific Populations (8.1)     ]  .



 Advise females of reproductive potential to avoid becoming pregnant while taking Lynparza. If contraceptive methods are being considered, use effective contraception during treatment and for at least one month after receiving the last dose of Lynparza [see     Use in Specific Populations (8.6)     ]  .
</Section>
  </Text>
  <Mentions><Mention id="M1" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="109" len="24" str="Myelodysplastic syndrome" /><Mention id="M2" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="134" len="22" str="Acute Myeloid Leukemia" /><Mention id="M3" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="209" len="11" str="Pneumonitis" /><Mention id="M4" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="337" len="6" str="anemia" /><Mention id="M5" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="345" len="6" str="nausea" /><Mention id="M6" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="353" len="7" str="fatigue" /><Mention id="M7" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="372" len="8" str="asthenia" /><Mention id="M8" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="383" len="8" str="vomiting" /><Mention id="M9" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="393" len="8" str="diarrhea" /><Mention id="M10" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="403" len="9" str="dysgeusia" /><Mention id="M11" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="414" len="9" str="dyspepsia" /><Mention id="M12" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="425" len="8" str="headache" /><Mention id="M13" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="435" len="18" str="decreased appetite" /><Mention id="M14" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="455" len="27" str="nasopharyngitis pharyngitis" /><Mention id="M15" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="483" len="3" str="URI" /><Mention id="M16" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="488" len="5" str="cough" /><Mention id="M17" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="495" len="10" str="arthralgia" /><Mention id="M18" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="506" len="20" str="musculoskeletal pain" /><Mention id="M19" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="528" len="7" str="myalgia" /><Mention id="M20" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="537" len="9" str="back pain" /><Mention id="M21" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="548" len="15" str="dermatitis rash" /><Mention id="M22" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="568" len="25" str="abdominal pain discomfort" /><Mention id="M23" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="624" len="24" str="laboratory abnormalities" /><Mention id="M24" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="662" len="22" str="increase in creatinine" /><Mention id="M25" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="686" len="33" str="mean corpuscular volume elevation" /><Mention id="M26" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="721" len="22" str="decrease in hemoglobin" /><Mention id="M27" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="745" len="23" str="decrease in lymphocytes" /><Mention id="M28" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="770" len="37" str="decrease in absolute neutrophil count" /><Mention id="M29" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="813" len="21" str="decrease in platelets" /><Mention id="M30" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="1896" len="5" str="death" /><Mention id="M31" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="1926" len="14" str="acute leukemia" /><Mention id="M32" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="1973" len="4" str="COPD" /><Mention id="M33" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="1979" len="24" str="cerebrovascular accident" /><Mention id="M34" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="2005" len="22" str="intestinal perforation" /><Mention id="M35" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="2029" len="18" str="pulmonary embolism" /><Mention id="M36" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="2049" len="6" str="sepsis" /><Mention id="M37" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="2061" len="14" str="suture rupture" /><Mention id="M38" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="2829" len="6" str="Anemia" /><Mention id="M39" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="3148" len="25" str="Abdominal pain discomfort" /><Mention id="M40" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="3411" len="18" str="Decreased appetite" /><Mention id="M41" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="3674" len="6" str="Nausea" /><Mention id="M42" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="3937" len="8" str="Vomiting" /><Mention id="M43" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="4200" len="8" str="Diarrhea" /><Mention id="M44" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="4463" len="9" str="Dyspepsia" /><Mention id="M45" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="4782" len="16" str="Fatigue asthenia" /><Mention id="M46" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="5148" len="15" str="Nasopharyngitis" /><Mention id="M47" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="5514" len="10" str="Arthralgia" /><Mention id="M48" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="5525" len="20" str="musculoskeletal pain" /><Mention id="M49" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="5777" len="7" str="Myalgia" /><Mention id="M50" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6523" len="22" str="Decrease in hemoglobin" /><Mention id="M51" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6547" len="6" str="anemia" /><Mention id="M52" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6626" len="37" str="Decrease in absolute neutrophil count" /><Mention id="M53" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6665" len="11" str="neutropenia" /><Mention id="M54" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6731" len="21" str="Decrease in platelets" /><Mention id="M55" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6754" len="16" str="thrombocytopenia" /><Mention id="M56" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6834" len="23" str="Decrease in lymphocytes" /><Mention id="M57" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6859" len="11" str="lymphopenia" /><Mention id="M58" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="6937" len="33" str="Mean corpuscular volume elevation" /><Mention id="M59" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7040" len="22" str="Increase in creatinine" /><Mention id="M60" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7186" len="24" str="laboratory abnormalities" /><Mention id="M61" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7318" len="5" str="cough" /><Mention id="M62" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7325" len="12" str="constipation" /><Mention id="M63" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7339" len="9" str="dysgeusia" /><Mention id="M64" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7350" len="16" str="peripheral edema" /><Mention id="M65" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7368" len="9" str="back pain" /><Mention id="M66" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7379" len="9" str="dizziness" /><Mention id="M67" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7390" len="8" str="headache" /><Mention id="M68" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7400" len="23" str="urinary tract infection" /><Mention id="M69" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7425" len="7" str="dyspnea" /><Mention id="M70" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7438" len="4" str="rash" /><Mention id="M71" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7480" len="24" str="laboratory abnormalities" /><Mention id="M72" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7611" len="10" str="leukopenia" /><Mention id="M73" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7623" len="10" str="stomatitis" /><Mention id="M74" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7635" len="21" str="peripheral neuropathy" /><Mention id="M75" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7658" len="7" str="pyrexia" /><Mention id="M76" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7667" len="14" str="hypomagnesemia" /><Mention id="M77" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7683" len="13" str="hyperglycemia" /><Mention id="M78" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7698" len="7" str="anxiety" /><Mention id="M79" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7707" len="10" str="depression" /><Mention id="M80" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7719" len="8" str="insomnia" /><Mention id="M81" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7729" len="7" str="dysuria" /><Mention id="M82" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7738" len="20" str="urinary incontinence" /><Mention id="M83" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7760" len="21" str="vulvovaginal disorder" /><Mention id="M84" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7783" len="16" str="dry skin eczema" /><Mention id="M85" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7801" len="8" str="pruritis" /><Mention id="M86" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7811" len="12" str="hypertension" /><Mention id="M87" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7825" len="17" str="venous thrombosis" /><Mention id="M88" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7854" len="18" str="pulmonary embolism" /><Mention id="M89" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="7879" len="9" str="hot flush" /><Mention id="M90" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="8822" len="8" str="Lynparza" /><Mention id="M91" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="8831" len="4" str="died" /><Mention id="M92" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="9340" len="6" str="Anemia" /><Mention id="M93" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="9621" len="25" str="Abdominal pain discomfort" /><Mention id="M94" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="9858" len="18" str="Decreased appetite" /><Mention id="M95" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="10095" len="6" str="Nausea" /><Mention id="M96" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="10332" len="8" str="Vomiting" /><Mention id="M97" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="10569" len="8" str="Diarrhea" /><Mention id="M98" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="10806" len="9" str="Dyspepsia" /><Mention id="M99" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11043" len="9" str="Dysgeusia" /><Mention id="M100" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11324" len="7" str="Fatigue" /><Mention id="M101" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11343" len="8" str="asthenia" /><Mention id="M102" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11353" len="8" str="lethargy" /><Mention id="M103" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11674" len="15" str="Nasopharyngitis" /><Mention id="M104" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11690" len="11" str="Pharyngitis" /><Mention id="M105" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="12034" len="10" str="Arthralgia" /><Mention id="M106" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="12045" len="20" str="Musculoskeletal pain" /><Mention id="M107" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="12482" len="7" str="Myalgia" /><Mention id="M108" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="12930" len="9" str="Back pain" /><Mention id="M109" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="13422" len="8" str="Headache" /><Mention id="M110" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="13779" len="5" str="Cough" /><Mention id="M111" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="14129" len="10" str="Dermatitis" /><Mention id="M112" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="14140" len="4" str="Rash" /><Mention id="M113" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="14634" len="22" str="Decrease in hemoglobin" /><Mention id="M114" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="14747" len="37" str="Decrease in absolute neutrophil count" /><Mention id="M115" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="14860" len="21" str="Decrease in platelets" /><Mention id="M116" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="14973" len="33" str="Mean corpuscular volume elevation" /><Mention id="M117" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="15086" len="22" str="Increase in creatinine" /><Mention id="M118" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="54" len="24" str="Myelodysplastic syndrome" /><Mention id="M119" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="79" len="22" str="Acute Myeloid Leukemia" /><Mention id="M120" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="104" len="7" str="MDS AML" /><Mention id="M121" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="175" len="5" str="fatal" /><Mention id="M122" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="316" len="11" str="Pneumonitis" /><Mention id="M123" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="391" len="5" str="fatal" /><Mention id="M124" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="505" len="21" str="Embryo Fetal toxicity" /><Mention id="M125" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="528" len="8" str="Lynparza" /><Mention id="M126" section="S2" type="Factor" start="537" len="3" str="can" /><Mention id="M127" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="547" len="10" str="fetal harm" /><Mention id="M128" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="744" len="24" str="Myelodysplastic syndrome" /><Mention id="M129" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="769" len="22" str="Acute Myeloid Leukemia" /><Mention id="M130" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="793" len="7" str="MDS AML" /><Mention id="M131" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="998" len="16" str="advanced cancers" /><Mention id="M132" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1058" len="7" str="MDS AML" /><Mention id="M133" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1110" len="23" str="advanced ovarian cancer" /><Mention id="M134" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1166" len="7" str="MDS AML" /><Mention id="M135" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1257" len="7" str="MDS AML" /><Mention id="M136" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1293" len="5" str="fatal" /><Mention id="M137" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="2131" len="11" str="Pneumonitis" /><Mention id="M138" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="2154" len="5" str="fatal" /><Mention id="M139" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="2518" len="8" str="Lynparza" /><Mention id="M140" section="S2" type="Factor" start="2527" len="3" str="can" /><Mention id="M141" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="2537" len="10" str="fetal harm" /><Mention id="M142" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="2657" len="11" str="teratogenic" /><Mention id="M143" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="2680" len="21" str="embryo fetal toxicity" /><Mention id="M144" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="548" len="10" str="dermatitis" /><Mention id="M145" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="559" len="4" str="rash" /><Mention id="M146" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="4782" len="7" str="Fatigue" /><Mention id="M147" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="4790" len="8" str="asthenia" /><Mention id="M148" section="S1" type="Severity" start="15188" len="7" str="Grade 1" /><Mention id="M149" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1058" len="3" str="MDS" /><Mention id="M150" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1062" len="3" str="AML" /><Mention id="M151" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1261" len="3" str="AML" /><Mention id="M152" section="S2" type="DrugClass" start="1333" len="8" str="Lynparza" /><Mention id="M153" section="S2" type="Animal" start="2705" len="4" str="rats" /><Mention id="M154" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="455" len="31" str="nasopharyngitis pharyngitis URI" /><Mention id="M155" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="495" len="31" str="arthralgia musculoskeletal pain" /><Mention id="M156" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="5514" len="31" str="Arthralgia musculoskeletal pain" /><Mention id="M157" section="S1" type="AdverseReaction" start="11674" len="27" str="Nasopharyngitis Pharyngitis" /><Mention id="M158" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1110" len="8" str="advanced" /><Mention id="M159" section="S2" type="AdverseReaction" start="1257" len="3" str="MDS" /></Mentions><Relations /><Reactions /></Label>